想在此处添加您的广告信息？立即联系 www.OpenSubtitles.org
-=圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hdscg.com/=-
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: 影子
翻译: BOBO金鱼 爱喝牛奶
翻译: lubi 轩一一 黄字君
校对: 浅陷夜蓝
我不知道
I don't know.
或许从一开始我们就注定不幸
Maybe we were doomed from the beginning.
我是说 不像爸爸是阳光先生
I mean, it's not like Dad was Mr. Sunshine.
有时候我认为他是我们一切问题的根源
Sometimes I think all our problems came directly from him.
但是他也带给我们很多美好的事物
But a lot of the good stuff did, too.
还记得他怎么叫我们吗?
Remember what he always called us?
恶魔两人组
The Gruesome Twosome.
他告诉我们不论怎样 都要在一起
He told us to stick together, no matter what.
上帝! 我们到底怎么回事?
God! What the hell happened to us?
崩溃姐弟
致相关人士
你好?
Hello?
嗨 请问是玛姬·迪恩吗?
Hi, is this Maggie Dean?
是的
Yes.
这里是洛杉矶长老会医院
This is L.A. Presbyterian Hospital.
我已经在国家谢绝来电注册名单里了
You know, I'm on the National Do Not Call Registry.
你怎么会有我电话?
How did you get this number?
我打来告知你 你的弟弟麦洛
I'm calling to inform you that your brother Milo
今日下午自杀未遂之后被送到我院救治
was admitted this afternoon after an attempted suicide.
他现在脱离危险了
He's okay.
迪恩女士?
Ms. Dean?
我在
Yes.
- 他没事了  - 好 谢谢
- He's okay.  - Good, thank you.
他大玩音乐是件好事
It's a good thing he was blasting his music.
有位邻居因为无法忍受把大楼管理员叫了过来
A neighbor complained and got the building manager.
这是他的遗书
Here's his note.
"致相关人士... 再见"
"To whom it may concern... See you later."
天啊
Jesus.
你们最后一次见面是什么时候?
When was the last time you saw each other?
大概有十年了
About 10 years.
嘿 麦洛
Hey, Milo.
嘿
Hey.
你染头发了
You changed your hair.
是的 它...
Oh, yeah. It's...
染成这种浅色有一段时间了吧
It's been light for a while, I guess.
瞧瞧你
Look at you.
是啊 看看我
Yeah, look at me.
又一个老掉牙的同志悲剧故事
Another tragic gay cliche.
我不知道你是否还喜欢炸苹果饼 也许口味没有詹森那家好
I don't know if you still like apple fritters. Probably not as good as Jensen's.
我不太饿
I'm not really hungry.
那我放这吧
I'll just leave them here.
医生说你还要在这里待多久?
How many days did they say you have to be in here?
一两天吧
A day or two.
有没有人...
Do you have anyone...
你一个人住?
Do you live alone?
嗯 我自己住
Yeah, I live alone.
好吧 如果有什么需要的话 我接下来的几天都会在
Well, I'm around the next couple days, if you need anything.
玛姬 我只是做了件蠢事而已
Maggie, this was just some stupid thing I did.
我当时喝醉了而且感觉很浮夸 所以...
I was drunk and feeling melodramatic, so...
你没必要过来
You didn't have to come here.
你走吧
You should go.
嘿
Hey.
他们告诉我你在这里
They told me you were down here.
我今天可以出院了
I get discharged today.
他们刚刚帮我叫了辆车 我以为你回家了
They just called me a cab. I thought you were going home.
为什么 因为你让我回去?
Why, because you told me to?
不 我命令你回去
No, because I asked you to.
怎么 你现在是医院的国王了?
What, are you king of the hospital now?
你读过马利与我吗?
Have you read Marley and Me?
读过 惨啊
Yeah, sad.
为什么很惨?
Why is it sad?
你不知道这个故事吗?
You don't know what happens?
不知道 所以我才读这本书
No, that's why I'm reading it.
噢 抱歉
Oh, sorry.
- 怎么了?  - 没什么
- What?  - Nothing.
- 什么 难道最后狗死了?  - 没有 我可没说
- What, does the dog die at the end?  - No, I didn't say that.
最后狗死了
The fucking dog dies at the end.
- 我没有... 我什么也没说  - 看看我还剩多少
- I didn't... I'm not saying anything.  - Look how much I had left.
抱歉我毁了你看书的心情
I'm sorry I ruined it.
玛姬 我知道狗死了
Maggie, I know the dog dies.
人人都知道狗死了
Everyone knows the dog dies.
狗就死在这本书里
It's the book where the dog dies.
混蛋
Asshole.
你又找回幽默感了
I see you're getting your sense of humor back.
是啊 没人能带走它
Yeah, they can't take that away from me.
我在想
I was thinking,
或许你会想搬来和我一起住?
Maybe you'd wanna come stay with me?
什么 搬回纽约?
What, back to New York?
嗯 我的意思是就待一段时间 直到你恢复为止
Yeah. I mean just for a little bit, until you feel better.
我有一间客房 而且你可以见见兰斯
I have a guest room and you can meet Lance finally.
每年这个时候尼亚克真的很美
Nyack's really beautiful this time of year.
所以医院危机顾问也找过你了 嗯?
So the crack team of hospital crisis counselors got to you, too, huh?
- 是我自己的决定  - 好吧 无所谓啦
- This was my decision.  - Yeah, whatever.
他们让你有负疚感不得不这么做
They guilted you into this.
你说得对 这主意也许不好
You're right. It's probably a bad idea.
等等 玛姬
Hey, Maggie.
我有一个水族箱
I have an aquarium
装满了肥嘟嘟非常可爱的金鱼
full of very beloved, fat goldfish.
在纽约你可以买新的金鱼
You can get new goldfish in New York.
欢迎回家
Welcome home.
嘿 你在这里啊
Hey, here he is.
- 兰斯  - 没错 就是我
- Lance.  - Yeah, sure am.
- 你好啊?  - 见到你很高兴
- How are ya?  - Great to meet you.
靠 抱歉 兄弟
Oh, shit. Sorry, man.
没关系 别担心 快痊愈了 所以没关系
It's okay. Don't worry about it. They're healing over, so it's fine.
终于见到你 我太兴奋了 你知道吗?
I'm so psyched to finally meet you, you know?
是啊 见到你 也一样
Yeah, you, too.
有血有肉 神秘的麦洛啊 是吧?
Mysterious Milo in the flesh, right?
好吧 实际上我穿着衣服呢 所以在见到我的血肉之前
Well, actually, I'm clothed now, so you'll have to get to know me
你对我的看法会稍微好一点
a little bit better before you see me in the flesh.
酷 酷
Cool, cool.
好吧 如果你有任何需要 我就在附近 所以直接叫我就好
Well, hey, if you need anything, I'm around, so don't hesitate to holler.
我就在... 我在做家务
I'm just... I'm doing a few chores.
好的 我会的 谢谢 谢谢你的招待
I will, I will, thank you. Thanks for having me.
好的 放轻松 兄弟
Okay, take it easy, amigo.
你也是 兄弟
You, too, amigo.
天啊 玛姬
Jesus, Maggie.
麦洛 你知道你野性又疯狂的姐姐做过什么吗?
So, Milo, you hear about your wild and crazy sister?
你知道... 他毫不知情?
Are you... He doesn't know?
你野性疯狂的姐姐一直在学习...
Your wild and crazy sister has been taking...
给我点击鼓声 来点 击鼓声 没错 大声点
Give me a drumroll. Come on, drumroll. Come on, louder.
水肺潜水课程
Scuba diving lessons.
- 没错  - 听起来不是很有意思吗?
- Yeah.  - Doesn't that sound like fun?
是啊 如果你喜欢水肺潜水
Yeah, if you like scuba diving, yeah.
我喜欢
I do.
她在为我们的热带夏威夷蜜月之旅做准备
She's preparing for our tropical Hawaiian honeymoon.
这技能会让人大跌眼镜
It's gonna be badass.
蜜月?
Honeymoon?
晚两年总比没有好 她出的主意 是你的想法
Better two years late than never. It was her idea. It was your idea.
- 迟做总比不做好  - 是啊
- Better late than never.  - Yeah.
她经常有很疯狂的念头
She's always getting crazy ideas.
上个月 是萨尔萨舞 你听过萨尔萨舞吗?
Last month, it was salsa dancing. Have you ever heard of salsa dancing?
就像一种西班牙风格的舞蹈?
It's kind of like a Spanish-flavored dancing?
是啊 没错 这个... 是的
Yeah, yeah, the... Yeah.
- 所以现在变成了水肺潜水  - 是的
- So now it's scuba diving.  - Yeah.
你去过吗?
You ever been?
- 没 没有  - 没有?
- No, no.  - No?
- 兄弟 你会爱上它的 简直太棒了  - 没错
- Dude, you'd love it. It's awesome.  - Right.
我和我的兄弟克雷格 几年前 我们去了哥斯达黎加
Me and my buddy Craig, a couple years ago, we went to Costa Rica.
在没遇到玛姬之前 玛姬未出现之前
This was before Maggie was on the scene. PM, Pre-Maggie.
我们第一次去潜水的时候
And the first time we go out on a dive,
我们看到了一只该死的海龟 非常罕见
we saw an effing sea turtle, which is very rare.
- 非常非常罕见  - 我认为挺正常的 不是吗?
- Incredibly rare.  - I think it's pretty normal, right?
- 看到海龟?  - 什么?
- Seeing sea turtles?  - What?
你潜水的时候 看到海龟? 我觉得这非常...
When you're diving, seeing sea turtles? I think that's very...
不 我觉得你想到的是那种普通的乌龟
No, I think you're thinking of just regular turtles
那种在池塘和小溪里经常见到
that you'd see in, like, a pond or a stream.
我刚刚说的那种是大自然里的海龟
I'm talking about a sea turtle in the wild.
我们当时离它很近 甚至可以触摸到它
We were swimming so close to it that you could practically touch it.
- 我可以告诉他吗? 可以吗?  - 没什么值得说的
- Is it okay if I tell him? Can I?  - Nothing really to tell yet.
准备好听点大新闻了吗?
You ready for some big news?
- 我们在尝试怀上孩子  - 真的吗?
- We're trying to get pregnant.  - Really?
- 我们在努力怀上宝宝  - 是的
- We are trying to get pregnant.  - Yeah.
而且我说 "我们"因为那样说不是性别歧视
And I say "we are"because it's not sexist that way.
- 对吧? 你告诉过我  - 没错
- Right? That's what you told me.  - Yeah.
我以为你不会想要孩子
I thought you never wanted to have kids.
是啊 我也许在高中还是什么时候说过
Well, I may have said that in high school or something,
但是显然人们的想法会改变
But obviously people change their minds on that.
不是 我... 真的太棒了
No, I... That's great.
我爱小孩子
I love kids.
除了肥肥的那种
Except the fat ones.
去他的小粪球 对吧?
Fuck those little turds, right?
他在开玩笑 他又自以为是了
He's kidding. He's being a smartass.
- 别介意  - 我逗你的
- Don't mind him.  - I'm messing with you.
我在想"喔 为什么这家伙不喜欢胖胖的孩子?"
I was like, "Whoa, what's this guy got against fat kids?"
- 不是 他...  - 我的意思是 我曾经是个小胖墩
- No, he's...  - I mean, I was a fat kid.
- 哦 是吗?  - 我当时像一辆坦克 没错
- Oh, you were?  - I was built like a damn tank, yeah.
- 她看过照片  - 但是还是非常可爱
- She's seen the pictures.  - It's pretty cute, though.
我看起来就像... 就像一只长着腿的小枕头
I look like a... Just a little pillow with legs.
- 一只棉花糖  - 是的
- A little marshmallow.  - Yeah.
嘿 这杯敬你们
Hey, here's to you guys.
- 谢谢 - 希望你们有胖乎乎而且幸福的孩子
- Thanks.  - May your kids be happy and fat.
太棒了 谢谢
Cool, man, thanks.
我是说 虽然还没动静 但是我们无疑在努力尝试了
I mean, it hasn't happened yet, but we're definitely giving it a go.
好吧 继续努力
Well, keep trying, guys.
我等不及要做古怪的同性恋叔叔了
I can't wait to be the creepy gay uncle.
- 你被雇用了  - 好吧
- You're hired.  - Okay.
这工作是你的了
You got the job.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.  - Hey.
- 搬进来了?  - 是的
- Settling in?  - Yeah.
是啊 就好像是玛莎·斯图尔特的仙境
No, yeah, it's like a Martha Stewart wonderland.
所以 你见过兰斯了
So, you met Lance.
没错 我见过兰斯了
Yeah, I met Lance.
他是不是最棒的?
Isn't he the best?
是啊 他就像一只大型拉布拉多猎犬
Yeah, he's like a big Labrador retriever.
大概是吧
Yeah, I guess.
他是地球上最好的人了
He's just the nicest guy on the planet.
我真是太走运了
I really lucked out.
是啊 你一直在追求这些啊
Yeah, you're really going for it.
- 这话什么意思?  - 你一直都想要啊
- What does that mean?  - You're going for it.
就像 你的工作 这套房子 这些家具 还有兰斯
Just, like, the job, the house, the furniture. The Lance.
我想我长大了吧
I guess I grew up.
- 所以 你怎么样?  - 什么我怎么样?
- So, what about you?  - What about me?
好吧 最后一次听到你的消息 你搬到洛杉矶做演员了?
Well, last I heard, you moved to L.A. to be an actor?
这大概 好像是十年前?
That was, like, 10 years ago?
- 没错 你没听说吗? 我得了奥斯卡  - 哦 很有趣
- Yeah, did you not hear? I won an Oscar.  - Oh, very funny.
是啊 我扮演了一个智障的乌克兰移民
Yeah, I played a retarded Ukrainian immigrant
他用棋艺激励了一群在布鲁克林读书的学童
who inspires a bunch of school kids in Brooklyn by playing chess.
- 别开玩笑了  - 就是这样
- Seriously.  - Seriously
没有经纪人的话 演戏真的有点难
Acting's kinda hard when you don't have an agent.
- 所以...  - 好吧 那你做什么谋生?
- So...  - Well, what are you doing for money?
让我猜猜看 讲黄色笑话的男妓...
Let me guess, male prostitute joke coming...
你希望我说什么 玛姬?
What do you want me to say, Maggie?
我在好莱坞一家劣等的观光饭馆做服务员
I wait tables at a shitty tourist restaurant in Hollywood.
无聊透顶 说完了 你还想知道什么?
It's fucking boring, the end. What do you want to know?
你看 我累了 我想睡了
You know, I'm tired. I'm gonna go to bed.
好吧 晚安
All right, good night.
靠
Shit.
共呼吸法的关键在于不要慌张
The key to buddy breathing is not to panic.
不要太紧张不然你会死的
Don't freak out or you'll die.
不许大力拉扯搭档的调节器
Don't yank the regulator away from your partner.
也不许反弹过去
Don't bogart the thing either.
就这样 所以 大家组成搭档 走吧 开始行动
All right, so, everybody partner up. Let's go, let's do it.
寻找对象吗?
Looking for a date?
搭档
A partner.
哦 是的 没错
Oh, yeah, sure. Okay.
这是我们目前畅销的一本书
This is a book that we're selling a lot more of.
它非常实际 更具有实践意义
It's just much more practical. It's much more hands-on.
- 听起来是不是...  - 听起来很棒
- Does that sound...  - It sounds perfect.
- 好的 很好 祝你好运  - 谢谢
- Okay, good. Yeah, good luck.  - Thank you.
惊喜
Surprise.
麦洛
Milo.
死而复生
Back from the dead.
你怎么会在这里?
What are you doing here?
我刚刚进城 想来打个招呼
I just rolled into town. I wanted to say hi.
不是 你来店里干什么?
No, what are you doing here at the store?
我在找最新的丹尼尔·斯蒂尔的小说
I am looking for the new Danielle Steel novel.
- 你该走了  - 不 不要 我... 我们去徒步旅行吧
- You should go.  - No, hey, no, I... Let's go hiking.
我们去凯特懒惰草垛酒店 而且 你知道
Let's go to Kate's Lazy Meadow and, you know,
- 去参加丰收节还有...  - 麦洛 你疯了
- go to the Harvest Festival and...  - Milo, you're out of your mind.
没有 里奇 我只是在想...
No, Rich, I just think...
别再来了
Don't come here again.
小伙子们什么时候出来?
When do the boys show up?
今晚是蕾丝之夜 亲爱的
It's Dyke Night, sweetie.
- 是什么?  - 蕾丝之夜
- It's what?  - Dyke Night.
蕾丝之夜?
Dyke Night?
我出现在蕾丝之夜?
I showed up on Dyke Night?
没错
Yeah.
靠
Shit.
- 天啊  - 嘿!
- Jesus.  - Hey!
卡尔角落酒吧那 去他妈的蕾丝之夜
Cal's Corner, fucking Dyke Night.
- 什么?  - 哦 天啊
- What?  - Oh, boy.
蕾丝之夜
Dyke Night.
麦洛 我们能早上再谈这些吗?
Milo, can we talk about this in the morning?
桑德拉和梅丽莎人都很好
Sandra and Melissa were very nice.
她们两个是教我玩飞镖的女同性恋
They were two lesbian ladies who taught me how to play darts.
但是她们不是我要找的
But they were not what I was looking for.
我要找到是
What I was looking for,
既然我们现在是亲戚了我就告诉你 兰斯
and you should know this since we're now related, Lance,
我在找鸡巴
I was looking for some cock.
好吧 麦洛 够了
Okay, Milo, enough.
我不找你 因为你和我姐姐结婚了
You're fine 'cause you're married to my sister.
- 你不能碰  - "不能碰"
- You're off-limits.  - "Off-limits."
只是告知你
Just letting you know,
你的兄弟们不管谁在附近 就...
if any of your little buddies around, just...
- 麦洛! 睡觉去  - 我会像牛排粘着饭一样贴上去
- Milo! Go to bed. - I will be on them like steak on rice.
够了 麦洛 晚安
Okay, Milo, good night.
我只想告诉你 我现在有点醉 抱歉了
I'm just letting you know. I'm a little tipsy. I'm sorry.
- 没事  - 别唧唧歪歪了
- That's okay.  - No shit.
- 麦洛 晚安  - 晚安
- Milo, good night.  - Good night.
- 关于昨天晚上...  - 你以后不能再这样了
- Yeah, about last night...  - You can't do stuff like that.
抱歉 我本来只是想缓解下压力 仅此而已 我只是...
Sorry, I was just trying to blow off some steam, that's all. I just...
兰斯和我聊过了 他说水坝的小径工程
So, Lance and I were talking, and he might need some help
还需要些人手
on this trail project at the dam.
就是做一些清理灌木工作等等
Just clearing brush and stuff.
水坝的小径工程?
A trail project at the dam?
对 他就是干这行的
Yeah. It's what he does.
什么意思? 清理灌木丛? 比如捡树枝?
What do you mean, clearing brush? Like picking up sticks?
灌木丛! 树枝呀树叶呀还有散灌木呀等等
Brush! Sticks and leaves and pieces of bushes and stuff.
- 接份活对你也好  - 所以 这是一份工作?
- It might be good for you. - So, it's like a job?
和兰斯多处处对你应该有好处的
It might be nice for you to spend time with him and stuff.
在满是灌木的大自然中呆着
Be out in nature with the brush.
我会有一件性感的制服吗?
Do I get a sexy outfit?
保证有
I'll make sure of it.
给你
Here.
我应该穿件长袖
Probably I should've worn longer sleeves.
是啊 不 我是说 下次
Yeah, no, I mean, next time, you know?
如果你穿了长袖 你就可以多铲点东西了
Cause then if you have long sleeves, you can make more of a scooping motion.
还可以每次多抓点树枝了
You might be able to get more with each grab, you know?
知道了 我理解
Yeah, no, I get it.
只是我不是那种户外型男人
I'm not really an outdoorsy kind of guy.
对 好了 别担心了 伙计
Right. Well, no worries, my man.
我卡车里还有一件羊毛外套
You know, I got an extra fleece in the truck.
- 要不要我去...  - 不用了 我很好
- You want me to go...  - No, no, I'm good.
- 谢了  - 你真没问题吗?
- Thank you. - You got it?
开什么玩笑
Oh, you gotta be fucking kidding me.
你还好吧? 没事吧?
You okay? You all right?
深呼吸 深呼吸
Take a breath. Take a breath.
刚刚在水下怎么了?
What happened down there?
没什么 我没事
Nothing, I'm fine.
- 真的吗?  - 我没事
- Yeah?  - I'm fine.
那好吧
All right.
有人在家吗?
Hello?
- 嗨.  - 手里拿的是什么?
- Hi.  - What the hell's that?
是给你第一天上班的礼物
Happy first day of work.
你没必要送我礼物的
You didn't have to do that.
怎么了? 不喜欢吗?
What, you don't like it?
怎么会 我喜欢 这礼物很赞
No, I love it. It's great.
我告诉某人我在城里
So, I told somebody that I was in town,
本来我没想到她会来的 你别吓到了
and I didn't think she would come, so don't freak out.
嗨 宝贝
Hi, Angel.
妈妈
Mother.
哎呀
Oh, dear.
好吧 玻璃碎了 大伙都别动 我去拿簸箕 你没事吧?
Okay, broken glass. Everybody freeze. I'm gonna go get a dustpan. You okay?
- 没事  - 那我去拿簸箕了
- Yeah.  - I'm gonna go get a dustpan.
好的
Okay.
- 那是坦纳吗?  - 不 那个是塔德
- So, that's Tanner?  - No, that's Tad.
坦纳是年纪最大的那个
Tanner's the oldest.
他们长得真像他们父亲
They look a lot like their father.
- 看见没?  - 我特别喜欢拱桥
- See?  - I love Arches.
- 看见了  - 大峡谷现在变得太过商业化
- Yeah.  - The Grand Canyon's gotten so commercial.
而拱桥却保留了它的精华 知道吗?
Arches has retained its essence, you know?
那是个精神圣地
It's just such a very, very spiritual place.
拱桥那里是最好的
Arches is rad.
大二春天的假期里我自驾游过那个地方
I actually road-tripped it down there spring break sophomore year.
- 太疯狂了 太不可思议了  - 干杯 干杯 我想和你们干一杯
- It's insane. Unbelievable.  - A toast? A toast? I want to make a toast.
致我一双漂亮的儿女 以及我可爱的女婿
To my beautiful, beautiful children, and to my lovely son-in-law.
愿阳光无尽的能量洒在你们身上
May the light embrace you with its energy infinite.
愿你们住在一个满是宁静祥和的地方
May you dwell in a place of peace and tolerance.
愿你们的岁月中永远充盈着温暖与理解
May you live in warmth and understanding for your days eternal.
- 阿门  - 是
- Amen.  - Yeah.
- 干杯  - 现在
- Cheers.  - Now.
亲爱的 谢谢
Darling, thank you.
你们什么时候去赛多纳看看我们?
So, when are you gonna come down and visit us in Sedona?
等我们被邀请了再去
I guess whenever we're invited.
天啊 你们直接去就好了
Oh, my God! You just have to show up.
就直接上门好了 我们不喜欢规划
Just drop in. We don't like to be scheduled.
- 好极了  - 很好 下周如何?
- Perfect.  - Great, so how's next week?
下周... 下周不是蛮方便
Next... That's not gonna actually be the best week.
那好 下下周我们去看你吧
Okay, great. The week after that. We can go then.
好吧...
Okay, well...
妈吗 那些羊驼怎样了?
Hey, Mom, how are the alpacas?
鉴于它们到处拉屎 我们不得不处理掉它们
We had to get rid of them. It was just too much poop.
你知道人们怎么说吗 每个人都会排泄 不是吗?
You know what they say, everybody poops, right?
我还小的时候 就以为女孩子不会便便
When I was a kid, I didn't think that girls pooped.
- 真的  - 我从来没有大便过
- Seriously.  - I've never taken a shit before.
麦洛
Milo.
对了 妈妈 你的静思会怎么样了?
So what about your insight retreats, Mom?
- 怎么了  - 最近会不会有?
- What about them?  - Do you have one coming up?
何出此言?
Why do you ask?
我只是想确定自己一生中最重要的日子
Oh, I just want to make sure I don't schedule
不会被放在同一天
the most important event of my life on the same day.
好吧 只是...
Okay, just...
你知道吗? 错过了你的婚礼我真的很难过
You know it broke my heart to miss the wedding.
事实上 我真感觉不到你在意
Actually, you know, I don't know that it did.
- 可是现在你在我们身边了 不是吗?  - 是的 谢谢
- You're here now, right?  - Yes, yes. Thank you.
你们都听到了我从没大便过吧?
Did everybody hear how I've never taken a shit before?
- 你们怀念那些岁月吗?  - 怀念
- Did you guys miss that?  - Yeah.
我们干嘛还要讨论那些不愉快的事情呢?
Why are we talking about such unpleasant things?
麦洛 亲爱的 你最近有何新进展?
Milo, what's new with you, darling?
我去拿点塔巴斯科辣酱
I'm gonna go grab the Tabasco.
你们有什么想要的吗?
Anybody like anything?
一切都好
Everything's great.
- 很好  - 好极了
- It's good.  - That's terrific.
一切都很好
Everything is terrific.
现在 呼气
Now, breathe out.
对
Yes.
你身心都得到净化了 睁开眼睛
You're cleansed. Open your eyes.
天啊! 你感觉如何?
Oh, my God! How do you feel?
很好 只是可能有点醉意
Good, yeah. I might be a little drunk.
你看起来完全不同了
You look completely different.
天啊! 感觉就是... 就是...
Oh, my God! There's just... There's a...
一种纯净的气息和光芒
A purity and a kind of a glow coming off you.
正从你的天灵盖散发出来
It's emanating from your crown chakra.
兰斯 你要不要来试试?
Lance, would you like to be cleansed?
我不需要了 谢谢 我早上才做过桑拿
I'm okay, thank you. I took a sauna this morning.
- 我现在觉得很好了  - 亲爱的 你呢?
- But I feel good.  - Sweetheart?
我一般不在喝酒的时候净化心灵
Oh, I don't usually drink and cleanse.
就像个人原则一样
Just, like, personal policy.
不过还是谢谢你
But thank you.
好吧 我想我也是时候回去了
Okay, I guess I should be heading back.
什么 这时候回亚利桑那?
What, like, back to Arizona?
及其巧合的是
Well, it's a terrific coincidence.
玛姬 你问过我关于静思会的事
You know, Maggie, you asked me about the insight retreat.
猜猜今年在哪里举行?
Guess where it is this year?
伍德斯托克 离这可近了
Woodstock. Around the corner.
- 你开玩笑吧  - 我是说 这也太...
- Oh, you've gotta be kidding.  - I mean, it's such a...
这真是太好了
This just worked out perfectly.
那是你来这里的原因吗?
So that's why you came here?
不 不
No, no.
我来这里是为了看看你们两
I came here to see you two.
闭嘴吧 妈吗
Oh, just shut up, Mother.
- 嘿  玛姬  - 这真是老把戏了
- Hey, Maggie.  - This is classic.
- 经典的一派胡言  - 好了 玛姬...
- Classic bullshit.  - Okay, Maggie...
但是我还是要表扬你 真的
I have to compliment you, though. I really do.
你表现的真不错
You gave it a good shot.
但是 我也不得不告诉你 你真不是一个当演员的料子
But I have to tell you, you're really not that good of an actress.
- 好吧 鉴于现在的气氛还是很好的...  - 不要再尝试了 朱蒂
- Okay. Well, as pleasant as this is...  - Stop trying, Judy.
不要再尝试了
Stop trying.
比起做一个不称职的母亲 这世上还有更多糟糕的事呢
There are worse things than being a shitty mother.
如果你话说完了
So, if you've finished
把不满都吐槽完了
vomiting all over me,
我只想说
I will just say
谢谢你招待我 还有麦洛 谢谢你的邀请
thank you for dinner, and, Milo, thank you for the invitation.
我很遗憾最后结果是这样
I'm sorry the night ended up being so toxic.
我只想你们两知道
I just want you both to know.
天啊
Oh, my God!
我向你们传递了光芒
I'm sending you the light.
晚安 兰斯
Good night, Lance.
晚安 朱蒂 我送送你
Good night, Judy. I'll walk you out.
好吧 至少她向我们传递了光芒
Well, at least she's sending us the light.
- 这是鞋子吗?  -对的 算是吧 他们是混合产物
- Are those shoes?  - Yeah, kinda. They're a hybrid.
什么的混合产物...
Hybrid of...
就是鞋子和脚丫子
Of, you know, just shoes and a foot.
人脚
The human foot.
大多数人吃东西都用刀叉的
You know, some people use a knife and fork for those things.
是吗? 好吧 我不同于大多数人 宝贝 我想这就是为什么你会爱上我
Yeah? Well, I'm not most people, babe, and I think that's why you love me.
就因为我特立独行
Cause I set myself aside from the pack.
- 是的  - 今晚见 好吧?
- Yeah.  - I'll see you tonight, okay?
我得走了
I gotta get going.
- 你来了  - 嘿
- Oh, there he is.  - Hey.
怎么了 长官?
What's up, chief?
没事
Nothing.
那就好 回来见
Okay, I'll check you two dudes later.
钱包 兰斯 在哪里? 宝贝 在哪里?
Wallet, Lance. Where is it, baby? Where is it?
他有不是这样的时候吗?
Is he ever not like that?
你知道我很高兴你在这里吧?
You know I'm happy that you're here, right?
- 又来了  - 还有你想呆多久都可以
- Here it comes.  - And you can stay as long as you need.
- 但是...  - 你在想什么?
- But...  - What do you think?
- 我觉得她会变得不一样的  - 这不重要
- I thought she'd be different.  - It doesn't matter.
关键是你没有权力在未经我同意的情况下带她回来
You had no right bringing her into this house without asking me.
遵命 长官
Yes, Warden.
你真的觉得她会不一样吗? 真的觉得她会关心咱们?
Did you really think she'd be different, that she'd actually give a shit about us?
- 或许吧  - 算了吧
- Maybe.  - Please.
自从爸爸... 她就和我们没关系了
She's been done with us ever since Dad...
我一点也不怪咱爸
I don't even blame him.
如果和她那样的人结婚 我也宁愿跳河自杀
Imagine being married to her. I'd probably jump off a bridge, too.
好吧
Okay.
我不想吃了 你来解决掉吧
I don't want this. Eat it.
好
Okay.
- 你现在感觉如何  - 很不错
- So, how you feel?  - I'm good.
- 真的吗?  - 真的
- Yeah?  - Yeah.
我就是对那天发生的事情有点尴尬
I'm a little embarrassed about the other day.
那时候我分心了 神游万里了
I was on planet Jupiter or something.
这没什么好担心的
Don't worry about it.
- 我就是个傻瓜  - 才不是呢
- I'm a doof.  - No.
你是我最喜欢的学员之一
You're one of my favorites.
曾经有人让我读读这本书
Someone told me to read this once.
去哪呢 头儿?
Where to, boss?
- 我需要你告诉我你出现在这里的原因  - 我...
- I need you to tell me why you're here.  - I'm...
我只是想和你说说话 只是想知道你是否一切安好
I just want to make conversation. I just want to see how you're doing.
- 真的吗?  - 真的 没别的了
- Really?  - Yeah, nothing more.
我绝对不会把你的蛋蛋割掉的
I'm not gonna chop your balls off just yet.
好吧 因为我近期真的不想再见到你了
Okay, cause I really wasn't expecting to see you anytime soon.
- 我知道  - 这样很奇怪
- I'm sure.  - This is weird.
我知道 我知道确实很奇怪
I know. I know it's weird.
你现在... 你究竟... 你现在好吗?
So, how are... What are you... How are you?
我很好 是的 很好 我有女朋友了
I'm good. Yeah, I'm good. I have a girlfriend.
她叫梅琳达 很不错的姑娘 是一名验光师
Melinda. She's great. She's an optometrist.
很好
Oh, cool.
她很适合我 她也和埃里克处得很融洽
Really good for me. She gets along with Eric really well.
- 埃里克?  - 我儿子
- Eric?  - My son.
对 你的儿子
Right, your son.
你现在住在这里吗?
Are you living here now?
不 不 我...
No, no, I...
只是暂时呆在这里 我来这儿只是为了... 我住在洛杉矶
Temporarily. I'm just here for... I live in L.A.
- 洛杉矶呀 挺好的  - 确实 确实
- L.A., that's cool.  - Yeah, yeah.
- 在那的生活如何?   - 蛮好的 一切都很顺利
- How's that?  - Good, good. It's going really well.
关键是在那里我一直很忙 知道吗?
I mean, the key is just staying busy, you know?
我一直在表演啊 试镜啊 我现在还有了自己的经纪人
I've just been acting and auditioning and I just got this agent.
- 真的吗?  - 对 我有自己的经纪人了
- Really?  - Yeah, I have an agent now.
- 经纪人 哇 太棒了  - 是啊
- An agent. Wow, that's impressive.  - Yeah.
你到城里来 除了跑到书店见我以外还有什么原因呢?
What brings you to town other than scaring the shit out of me at a bookstore?
我只是想来见你而已
Yeah, that was my sole purpose.
不 我... 有一个作家休养地
No, I... There's a writer's retreat.
而我正在写一部独角戏
You know, I'm writing this one-man show.
对于这我一点也不感到惊讶 你写作一直很好
Well, it doesn't surprise me at all. You were always a great writer.
那是因为我有一个...
Oh, well, I had a...
很好的导师
I had a good teacher.
在夏威夷岛屿的科纳海滨的帕瓦伊海湾 有一个小海湾
It's a little cove off the Pawai Bay on the Kona Coast, off the Big Island.
我的朋友麦克自从05年起就一直呆在那儿了
My mate Mike has been there since 05
参加一些小组织潜水 我和你说哦...
taking small groups diving, and I'm telling you...
- 美吗?  - 美极了
- Pretty?  - It's stunning.
你可以看见海龟 蝠鲼 大青鲨
Sea turtles, manta rays, blue sharks.
听起来很不可思议
That sounds incredible.
除了鲨鱼 我觉得
Except for the sharks, I guess.
它们是无害的
They're harmless.
而且
Besides,
由你来应付区区一只小小老鲨鱼是没有问题的
you could handle a little old shark.
- 你要再来一杯吗?  - 好
- You want another?  - Yeah.
还是不要了
No. No.
我觉得我已经喝多了
I think I've filled my quota.
我该走了
I should go.
- 可是我还没喝完呢  - 来 我来
- I haven't finished my drink yet.  - Here, I'll take that.
好了 我们撤吧
Okay, there we go.
玩得很开心
That was fun.
我们一起喝了酒 感觉很不错 谢谢你
We had drinks. That was nice. Thank you.
潜水课上见
I will see you in class.
天啊
Shit.
亲爱的?
Sweetie?
嗯?
Yeah?
我们的特色披萨吃完了吗?
Are we out of pizza pockets?
应该是吧
I think so.
那你能把它们写在购物清单里吗?
Well, can you put them on the list, please?
亲爱的?
Honey?
你下班以后会来接我吗?
So, you'll pick me up after work?
好的
Okay.
- 好吧 那 祝你今天工作愉快  - 一定
- All right, well, have a good day at work.  - I will.
- 问兰斯好  - 我会的
- Tell Lance I say hi.  - I will.
好的
Okay. All right.
- 拜 祝你一天顺利  - 回见 拜
- Bye, have a good day.  - See ya, bye.
拜
Bye.
怎么了?
What's up?
你觉得我应该要一个孩子吗?
Do you think I should have a baby?
你说我会不会是一个好妈妈?
I mean, do you think I would be a good mom?
我不知道
I don't know.
我觉得你肯定会很投入
I mean, I think you'd be very attentive.
- 好吧  - 可能还有点过分保护
- Okay.  - And maybe a bit overprotective.
易怒
Uptight.
呃 谢谢了
Gee, thanks.
我只是照实说啊 我...
No, I'm just being honest, I'm...
这问题太难回答了 抱歉
It's a loaded question. I'm sorry.
我觉得我会是一位出色的母亲
I think I'd be an excellent mom.
好啊
Okay.
你想让我说什么?
What do you want me to say?
别让我觉得自己糟糕透顶好不好?
How about something that doesn't make me feel like a piece of shit?
你真他妈自私 麦洛 我算见识了
You know, you're so goddamn selfish, Milo, it's mind-blowing.
玛姬
Maggie.
哦 玛姬 她就是那样 很经典
Oh, that's classic Maggie, man. Classic.
是啊 她刚才歇斯底里
Yeah, she just jumped down my throat.
- 很疯狂  - 你踩到地雷了 哥们
- It was crazy.  - Land mines, man.
就像有时候我和她在公园散步
It's like sometimes she and I will be strolling through the park
一直处得非常开心 然后 咔嘭 你知道?
laughing, getting along perfect, and then, kaboom, you know?
一个该死的地雷把我炸蒙了
A freakin' land mine blows my nuts off.
- 你能理解么?  - 是的
- You know?  - Yeah.
我心想说"刚才我的坚果就在这儿啊"
And I'll think, "Oh, I could've sworn my nuts were there a minute ago."
"不知道它们被炸哪儿去了"
"I wonder where they went."
- 没有坚果诶  - 哦 在那儿呢
- No nuts.  - Oh, there they are.
它们被炸飞出房间
They got blown clear across the room.
正顺着那墙滑下来 我的坚果
They're sliding down that wall over there. My nuts.
但是后来我仔细一想
And then, you know, when I think about it,
可能是我犯错在先 所以我就跟她道歉
it was probably my fault in the first place, so I'll just apologize to her.
大概我之前说了一些愚蠢或者伤人的话
I probably said something stupid or insensitive,
所以我就告诉她我很抱歉 然后就好了
so I'll just tell her that I was sorry, and then it's fine.
小心地雷 兄弟
Land mines, dude.
你在这里啊
There she is.
你的车准备好了
Your chariot awaits.
好吧 我错了
All right, look, I'm sorry.
我是个傻瓜
I'm an idiot.
还有什么我不知道的?
So what else is new?
你会成为一个出色的母亲 好吗?
You'd make an amazing mother, okay?
可是我易怒
I thought I was too uptight.
我刚才那样说是为了回避你真正的问题
I just said that so I didn't have to talk
你的病态肥胖症
about the real issue, which is your morbid obesity.
我很吃惊你居然出得去屋子
I'm surprised you can even leave the house.
你上次洗牙是什么时候?
When was the last time you had your teeth cleaned?
- 不 不 不 不 不 不  - 来嘛
- No. No, no, no, no, no.  - Come on.
- 不要  - 嘿 我可是有执照的牙科保健师
- No.  - Hey, I am a licensed dental hygienist.
你不想看看我怎么工作的?
Don't you want to see me work?
不想
No.
星球那么多 时间却很少
There are so many planets, yet so little time.
好了 我要把这个摘下来
All right, okay, I'm gonna take this.
- 等等 你干嘛?  - 麦洛 别闹了
- Wait, what are you doing?  - Milo, that's enough.
- 等等 等等 我还没看完呢  - 正经点 快松手
- Wait, wait, wait. I'm not done yet. - Come on, seriously, let go.
松手
Let go.
- 我没完呢  - 别闹了
- I'm not done.  - Stop.
- 好了 准备好没?  - 稍等 好了
- Okay, okay, are you ready?  - I'm sorry. Okay.
洗牙需要很小心
'Cause this is serious stuff here.
再漱几秒
A few more seconds.
把那个给我! 给我
Give that to me! Give it to me.
吐出来 吐那里边
Spit. Spit in there.
- 不好意思 我觉得这个坏了  - 哦 我的...
- Sorry, I think this is broken.  - Oh, my...
麦洛 住手
Milo, stop.
你得把那东西修好
That thing, you gotta have that thing fixed.
天啊!
My God!
你知道吗? 你别总那么正经
You know what? You need to take the edge off.
好吧 没办法
Yeah, right. No.
大家都在搞怪 你要是不活泼点 以后就没人跟你说话了
Everybody's doing it. If you don't do it, no one will ever talk to you.
我不干
I'm not doing it.
罗斯和蒂娜 还有艾米丽和凯西都这么做
Ross is doing it, Tina's doing it, Emily's doing it, Casey's doing it.
- 莎伦也会搞怪  - 莎伦肯定不会搞怪
- Shannon is doing it.  - Shannon cannot be doing it.
- 还有埃里克·T和埃里克·S  - 还有埃里克·T和埃里克·S?
- Eric T. and Eric S.  - Eric T. and Eric S., too?
埃里克·T和埃里克·S都会这样做
Eric S. and Eric T. are both doing it.
我不干
I'm not doing it.
我要很认真地问你个问题
I have a very serious question for you.
你能跟我去舞会吗?
Will you go to prom with me?
我觉得你要放屁
I think you're gassy.
不会打疼的 准备好了?
It's okay, this won't hurt. Ready?
- 疼吗?  - 你胳膊肘撞到我肉了
- That hurt?  - Your elbow went into my arm muscle.
"你的胳膊肘撞到我肉了 先生"
"Your elbow went into my arm muscle, mister."
"哦 这下我没法送报纸了"
"Oh, my paper route's gonna be screwed."
我要出去了
I'm getting out of here.
- 这笑话不错  - 谢了
- That was a good joke.  - Thanks.
- 有件事情我要告诉你 玛姬  - 什么?
- I have to tell you something, Maggie.  - What?
上个月在洛杉矶...
Last month in L.A...
怎么了? 怎么了?
What? What?
我给一个女孩口交
I ate pussy.
什么?
What?
- 怎么会?  - 我知道 挺不光彩的
- What?  - I know, I'm not proud of it.
为什么啊? 跟谁啊?
Why? How? Why? Who?
她看着像黛比·哈利年轻的时候
She looked like a young Debbie Harry.
我当时喝醉了而且很好奇 抵不住诱惑
I was drunk and curious. I just couldn't resist.
哦 我的天啊
Oh, my gosh.
好吧 然后... 结论是?
Well, what... How... Verdict?
这么说吧 像体验大海
I was a little out to sea. I'll tell you that.
体验潮湿有风暴的海
Out in a wet, stormy,
气味刺鼻的海
pungent sea.
- 好了 该你了  - 该我了?
- All right, now your turn.  - My turn?
我跟你说了一个秘密 你也得告诉我一个
I told you a secret. You have to tell me a secret.
- 我没有秘密  - 玛姬
- I don't have any secrets.  - Maggie.
玛姬·迪恩
Maggie Dean.
我在节育
I'm on birth control.
真的吗?
Really?
是的
Yeah.
我把药片藏在卫生间的小筐里
I hide it in a basket in the bathroom.
我估计兰斯短时间内不会发现
I figure Lance won't be looking for butterfly
药片藏在蝴蝶型香皂盒里
decorative soaps anytime soon.
所以很糟糕
So, it's terrible.
为什么不跟兰斯坦白说你还没准备好要孩子?
Wouldn't it be easier just to tell Lance you're not ready to have a kid?
是啊
Yeah.
那就简单多了
It would be a lot easier.
但是情况有点复杂
But there's a little more to it than that.
还有什么?
What?
- 真的很糟  - 什么?
- It's really bad.  - What?
我跟我的潜水教练上床了
I slept with my scuba instructor.
玛姬
Maggie.
我知道 听着像色情片
I know, it sounds like a porno.
就一次?
Just once?
- 跟他吗?  - "跟他"?
- With him?  - "With him"?
是啊 六个月前我上了一门法式烹饪课
Yeah. I took a French cooking class like six months ago.
玛姬!
Maggie!
还有自然摄影课... 我认识了这个人
And a nature photography course... I met this guy.
听起来你有恋物癖
It's a fetish is what it sounds like.
如果被兰斯发现 他肯定会崩溃
If Lance finds out, it will destroy him
而我自己也没办法活下去
and I will not be able to live with myself.
求你说点什么
Please say something.
也许兰斯不是你喜欢的类型
I guess Lance just doesn't do it for you.
但是为什么呢? 他人那么好
But why? He's so great.
他非常贴心 可爱善良 而且肯定会是一个好爸爸
He's so sweet and cute and nice and he would make such a great dad,
兰斯跟那些我约会过的混蛋们相比
and he is the polar opposite of all the assholes
简直是天壤之别
that I'm used to dating.
我这种荡妇不配做他的妻子
He doesn't deserve a fucking whore as a wife.
- 你不是荡妇  - 哦 是吗?
- You're not a whore.  - Oh, really?
- 所以请别那么说  - 那你觉得我是什么?
- So don't say that, please.  - What would you call it, then?
你是一个放纵的有荡妇倾向的家庭主妇
You're a restless housewife with whore-like tendencies.
算了吧
Shut up.
都差不多
It doesn't help.
你爱他吗?
Do you love him?
是的 我爱他 他是...
Yeah, I do. He's...
他挺好的
He's good.
也许挺好不是你的风格
Maybe good isn't your thing.
也许吧
Maybe.
我该怎么办?
What am I gonna do?
跟你的同性恋弟弟一起放屁怎么样?
You're gonna do a bunch of nitrous with your gay brother?
要不要躺下聊会?
You wanna talk about this more downstairs?
好啊
Sure.
- 哦 我后背疼  - 是啊 我的脊椎
- Oh, this hurts my back.  - Me, too, my spine.
- 我为啥要说"躺下聊会"?  - 不知道
- Why did I say, "Let's talk downstairs"?  - I don't know.
- 等一下 几点了?  - 不知道
- Wait, what time is it?  - I don't know.
该死
Shit.
- 怎么了?  - 快点 我们得走了
- What?  - Come on, we gotta go.
- 为什么?  - 我要去见个人
- Why?  - I have a meeting.
你要去见个人? 见谁?
You have a meeting? With who?
高中的凯文·克兰西
With Kevin Clancy from high school.
- 真的吗?  - 是的
- Really?  - Yeah.
不错 我能去吗?
Cool. Can I come?
不要 我觉得他希望是那种一对一的会面
No. I think he wanted to make it kind of like a one-on-one kind of meeting.
- 很奇怪吧 抱歉  - 没事
- Is that weird? I'm sorry.  - No.
- 不要紧  - 可以吗?
- No, it's fine.  - Is that cool?
- 嗯 嗯 嗯  - 那我们快走吧
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.  - All right, we gotta go, though.
走吧
We gotta go.
天啊! 我不行了
Oh, my God! You're killing me.
别别别 听这个 就好像说"麦尔维尔 兄弟 拜托"
No, no, no, but, listen, it's like, "Melville, dude, please,
"拜托你就写一个人捕鲸鱼的故事"
"just write me a story about a whale, a guy who catches a whale."
"你干嘛要费八百页写捕鲸的历史"
"Why does it have to be 800 pages of the history of whaling"
"还有那些狗屁的存在危机?"
"and all this existential crisis bullshit?"
就像一篇很奇怪搞笑丰富鲜活的文章从来没人看一样
Like, who gives a shit when the writing is that weird and funny and rich and alive
我提到"奇怪的"了吗?
and did I mention weird?
不过你明白我的意思对吧? 除非与社会阶层有关
You know what I mean, though? But with class.
或者矫揉造作 矫揉造作
And pretentious. And pretentious.
有一份白鲸的插图画我觉得你会喜欢
There's a great Moby Dick illustrated that I think you'd love.
- 最后是一张出水的鲸鱼  - 去你的
- There's a pop-up whale at the end.  - Fuck you.
我给过你鲸鱼是吧?
Didn't I give you a whale?
我记得给过 是一个铜质小雕像
I feel like I gave you, like, a copper figurine
送你的生日礼物 我是在...
for your birthday that I got at that...
哇哦! 你随身带着?
Wow! You carry that with you?
我猜它可能会带来好运气之类的
I don't know. It's, like, a little good luck charm or something.
没错
Well, it's working.
- 是吗? 我不确定  - 是的
- Is it? I don't know if it is.  - Yeah.
没错 洛杉矶经纪人之星
Yeah, Mr. Fancy L.A. Agent.
这鲸鱼我应该自己留着
I should've kept that whale for myself.
没什么大不了的 他不是知名经纪人
It's not that big of a deal. He's not that big of an agent.
我觉得很了不起
I think it's incredible.
我早就知道你的人生会很精彩
I always knew you'd do something amazing with your life.
我为你自豪 麦洛
I'm proud of you, Milo.
你想离开这里吗?
Do you wanna get out of here?
那些龙虾箱子能把人打倒
Those lobster cages can knock you right off.
你说什么?
What?
实际上应该叫龙虾罐
Well, actually, they're called lobster pots,
但它们能把这些人打下甲板
but they can knock these guys right off the deck.
真的很危险
They're real dangerous.
我觉得那些是螃蟹
I think those are crabs.
- 在哪里?  - 电视上那些
- Where?  - Everywhere.
哦 可能是吧
Oh, yeah, maybe they are.
不 那就是螃蟹
No, they are.
麦洛最近怎么样?
So, how's Milo working out?
挺好的 他是在尽最大努力 但是他... 他在努力
Good. He's definitely doing his best, but he's been... He's trying.
那就好
Good.
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
我真的爱你
I really love you.
谢谢
Thank you.
天啊 我不敢相信他都十六岁了
God, I can't believe he's 16.
有个这么大的孩子很奇怪
It's strange, man. Having a kid that old.
他刚刚考了驾照
He just got his license.
我心想"真的吗?"
I'm like, "Really?"
"我老到孩子都能开车了?"
"I'm old enough to have a kid who can drive?"
天啊!
My God!
你儿子知道我跟你的事吗?
Does he know about me and you?
不知道 天啊 当然不知道
No, no, God, no.
他知道我曾经教书
He knows I used to teach
有时候他问我为什么不教了 但是...
and sometimes he asks why I stopped, you know, but...
你怎么跟他说的?
What do you tell him?
我说我不适合教书
That it wasn't my thing.
抱歉 里奇
I'm sorry, Rich.
不 麦洛 你根本不需要道歉
No, Milo, you don't ever have to apologize.
你什么也没做错 你明白吗?
You didn't do anything wrong. You understand me?
好的
Okay.
我知道我们的关系奇怪糟糕而且违法
Look, I know what happened was weird and illegal and shit,
但这对我很重要
but it really meant something to me.
我们是成年人
And we're adults.
我现在是成年人了
Well, I'm an adult.
天啊 我感觉像是新生在邀请大四的跳舞
God, I feel like the freshman asking the senior to the dance.
这就是问题 有...
That's part of the problem. There's...
我们之间就像高低年级 总有差距
There's a freshman/senior dynamic between us.
可以没有的
There doesn't have to be.
麦洛 起床 兰斯十分钟以后就走了
Milo, get up. Lance is leaving in 10 minutes.
麦洛?
Milo?
麦洛 是你手机响吗?
Milo, is that your phone?
哦 该死 几点了?
Oh, shit, what time is it?
九点多
It's after 9:00.
该死 我迟到了
Fuck, I'm late for work.
咱俩都迟到了
You and me both.
这个给你
So, here.
- "曼哈顿日出" - 这是部浪漫喜剧
- "Sunrise in Manhattan." - It's a romantic comedy.
- 有关什么的 巴尔扎克和福柯?  - 不是 其实情节很简单
- About what, Balzac and Foucault?  - No, it's actually pretty straightforward.
就像是詹妮弗·安妮斯顿或者凯特·哈德森演的那种
I wrote it for, you know, like, Jennifer Aniston or Kate Hudson.
我不想太冒昧
And I don't want to be presumptuous,
但是我觉得如果你想看
but I thought, you know, if you wanted to read it
或者你喜欢的话 顺便帮我拿给你经纪人看看?
and maybe if you liked it, you could pass it along to your agent?
好的 好的 没问题
Yeah, okay. Yeah, totally.
- 当然 我很乐意...  - 太好了
- Yeah, I could totally...  - Cool.
帮你交过去如果... 我会读的
Pass it on if... I'll read it.
- 那太棒了  - 嗯
- Cool.  - Yeah.
我有点儿... 我想你应该走了
I kind of... I need you to leave.
好 嗯 当然
Okay. Yeah, sure.
- 昨晚很开心  - 是啊
- Last night was fun.  - Yeah.
有点昨日重现的感觉啊
Kind of a blast from the past.
嗯 还有... 走的时候别忘了锁门
Yeah, and... make sure the door locks when you close it.
迪恩小姐 你好啊
Greetings, Ms. Dean.
什么风把你吹来了?
What brings you around these parts?
那是个错误
It was a mistake.
好吧
All right.
我的意思是 所有的一切 都是错误
I mean it, the whole thing.
好吧
Fine.
说完了?
Is that all?
嗯 说完了
Yeah. Yeah, that's all.
你干嘛?
What are you doing?
不 比利 我认真的
No, Billy, I'm serious.
不
No.
卧槽! 扯淡! 卧槽! 卧槽!
Bullshit! Bullshit! Bullshit! Bullshit.
扯淡
Bullshit.
卧槽!
Bull shit.
好哇
Hello.
你早上干嘛去了?
Where were you this morning?
唔 凯文有个朋友 然后昨晚我们... 很爽哦
Well, Kevin had a friend, and last night, I got lucky.
唔 你都没赶上上班 还爽毛线啊
Well, you missed work, so, not cool.
就是迟了一小会儿嘛 兰斯理解的
I was a little late. Lance understood.
麦洛 你得学会把你的日子安排得井井有条
You have to get your shit together, Milo.
这话从你嘴里说出来真是有点稀罕
That is a very interesting statement coming from you.
- 你知道吗?  - 什么?
- You know what?  - What?
哇哦
Wow.
你干嘛?
What are you doing?
麦洛
Milo.
# 凝望你的双眼 仿佛看到伊甸园 #
# Looking in your eyes I see a paradise #
# 这世界美妙 不可思议到极点 #
# This world that I found is too good to be true #
# 站在你的身边 想与你分享万千 #
# Standing here beside you, want so much to give you #
# 这爱埋藏于心 对你深深迷恋 #
# this love in my heart that I'm feeling for you #
# 他们尽管笑我们疯癫 #
# Let them say we're crazy #
# 与我无关 #
# I don't care about that #
# 只要把手给我 宝贝 #
# Put your hand in my hand, baby #
# 别回头看 #
# Don't ever look back #
# 就让这个世界 分崩离析 #
# Let the world around us just fall apart #
# 只要心在一起爱就不会熄 #
# Baby, we can make it if we're heart to heart #
# 我们为梦想一起努力 #
# And we can build this dream together #
# 永远充满活力 #
# Standing strong forever #
# 此刻无人能敌 #
# Nothing's gonna stop us now #
# 就算真爱萎靡 #
# And if this world runs out of lovers #
# 你我相伴相依 #
# We'll still have each other #
# 此刻无人能敌 #
# Nothing's gonna stop us #
# Nothing's gonna stop us now #
成 懂了
Okay, I got it.
# 幸好与你遇见 #
# I'm so glad I found you #
# 不想同你再见 #
# I'm not gonna lose you #
# 无论前路何方 我都与你相伴 #
# Whatever it takes, I will stay here with you　#
# 快乐与你分享 悲伤为你分担 #
# Take it to the good times, see it through the bad times #
# 无论面对什么 我都心甘情愿 #
# Whatever it takes is what I'm gonna do #
# 别人尽管笑我们疯狂 #
# Let them say we're crazy #
# 他们哪儿懂? #
# What do they know? #
# 用你双臂环绕住我 宝贝 永远别松 #
# Put your arms around me, baby, don't ever let go #
# 就让这个世界 分崩离析 #
# Let the world around us just fall apart #
# 只要心在一起爱就不会熄 #
# Baby, we can make it if we're heart to heart #
# 我们为梦想一起努力 #
# And we can build this dream together #
# 永远充满活力 #
# Standing strong forever #
# 此刻无人能敌 #
# Nothing's gonna stop us now #
# 就算真爱萎靡 #
# And if this world runs out of lovers #
# 我们相伴相依 #
# We'll still have each other #
# 此刻无人能敌 此刻无人能敌 #
# Nothing's gonna stop us, nothing's gonna stop us #
# 哦 你是我的唯一 #
# Ooh, all that I need is you #
# 我所有的希冀 #
# All that I ever need #
# 我所有的努力 #
# All that I want to do #
# 就是能永远和你 #
# Is hold you forever #
# 永远在一起 #
# Ever and ever #
# 我们为梦想一起努力 #
# And we can build this dream together #
# 永远充满活力... #
# Standing strong forever... #
嗨
Hi.
你爸回来了没?
Is your dad home?
嗯 等下
Yeah, hold on.
爸 门口有人找
Dad, some guy's at the door for you.
抱歉 我以为你只有...
I'm sorry, I thought you had him...
你干嘛? 你不能来这里
What are you doing? You can't be here.
我儿子在这儿
That's my kid in there.
好吧 我以为你只有周末才会接他过来
Okay, I thought you only had him on the weekends.
我有我的生活 麦洛 一个完整的生活
I have a life, Milo. A whole life.
给我来一杯金快活龙舌兰 谢谢
Give me a shot of Cuervo, please.
再来一杯 成么?
Can I have another one, please?
嘿
Hey.
你在这儿干什么?
What are you doing up here?
我在等你啊 警察大哥
I'm waiting for you, Mr. Big Officer Man.
你胡说八道些什么?
The fuck you say?
谢谢 真的非常感谢
Thank you. Thank you very much.
没事儿 好好照顾他
No problem. Take care, now.
谢谢
Thanks.
玛姬 别害怕
Maggie, don't freak out.
怎么了?
What is going on?
你不会懂的
You wouldn't understand.
试着跟我说说吧 说不定我能理解呢
Try me. You might be surprised.
我很沮丧 还做了不少蠢事 就这样
I get depressed about my life and I do stupid things. That's it.
生活中我们都会难过 麦洛
We all get sad about our lives, Milo.
但那并不意味着我们可以跳楼
That doesn't mean we go jumping off of rooftops.
我没打算跳
I wasn't gonna jump.
好吧 可是我怎么知道呢?
Okay, well, how do I know that?
好吧 对不起
Okay, I'm sorry.
我真是无法接受 麦洛 我现在无法接受 我做不到
I can't take this, Milo. I can't right now. I can't.
嘿 对不起
Hey, I'm sorry.
你还记得咱们八年级时候的那个贾斯汀·梅尔?
Do you remember Justin Meyer in eighth grade?
乔克 那傻逼 那时候老和我过不去的那个?
Jock, asshole, he used to fuck with me all the time?
老爸 他跟我说... 他说 "贾斯汀这样的人 "
Dad, he told me... He said, "Guys like Justin,
这样的人 高中就是他们能达到的最高水平
like, high school is the best it's ever gonna get for them.
他们在高中达到人生顶峰
They're gonna peak in high school,
然后余生都在走下坡路 一事无成 "
and the rest of their life is just gonna be a disappointment. "
但是像我这样的孩子
And that kids like me,
会在高中以后才开始发光发热
that I would soar after high school.
而且 事实上 我可以坐在这里
And, in fact, I would sit there,
想象十年后的未来
I would fast-forward 10 years into the future
想象在我们的高中同学会上
and I would think about our high school reunion
我再次遇到贾斯汀 他变得又胖又秃
and seeing Justin, and he would just be this fat, balding guy
就像 你能想象的 就像那些运动商店的服务员
who, you know, is the assistant manager at some sporting goods store,
而我 则会成为有名的演员
and I would be this famous actor
住在洛杉矶 或者纽约 然后有一个同样英俊的男友
who lives in L.A. or New York and I have this beautiful boyfriend.
生活得很幸福
And I'm happy.
你知道我在网上又找到贾斯汀了吗?
Do you know I looked Justin up online?
你知道他现在在做什么吗?
And do you know what he's doing now?
他是个电气工程师
He's an electrician,
他有一个漂亮媳妇和两个可爱的女儿
and he has two beautiful daughters and a pretty wife.
他很幸福
And he's happy.
而这一切都说明...
And it turns out that...
这一切都说明我才是那个在高中达到顶峰的人
It just turns out that I'm the one that peaked in high school.
你想 如果这都不让人沮丧 那...
You know, if that's not depressing, then...
就这样吗 亲爱的?
So, that's it, sweetie?
你不是个著名演员?
You're not a famous actor?
可我得告诉你 没人是什么所谓的名演员
Cause I got news for you. No one's a famous actor.
乔治克鲁尼就很有名
George Clooney's a famous actor.
好吧 乔治克鲁尼 凡事总有例外
Okay, George Clooney, I guess that's one exception.
但是余下的我们大部分人都只是芸芸众生
But the rest of us are just walking around
拼尽全力
trying not to be disappointed
不让自己对自己的人生失望
with the way that our lives turned out.
或者 我们去应对或者...
And either we find a way to deal or...
我只是想确定 你不会离开我
I need to know you're not gonna check out on me.
我会尽力的
I'll do my best.
什么?
What?
你在干吗?
What are you doing?
肯定就放在这里面
It's got to be in here somewhere.
哦 上帝啊!
Oh, my God!
哇哦!
Wow!
在这儿! 我找到了!
Oh, here it is! I found it!
天啊! 你还留着这种东西?
Oh, my God! You still have that thing?
- 咱们该走了  - 啥?
- We're going out.  - What?
今天是万圣节 兰斯有一场虚拟足球赛
It is Halloween, Lance is at fantasy football,
我说你会盛装出席 要么漂亮 要么逗逼
I say you put on something pretty and/or freaky.
当然最好两个都有
Preferably both.
好啊
Yeah.
我自己能画得更好
I can do this better myself.
不要 我想给你画
No, I wanna do it.
好啦
Okay.
不喜欢就说
Tell me if you don't like it.
如果我不喜欢 我会立刻告诉你
I will tell you immediately if I don't like it.
怎么样 是不是很惊喜?
Is that a good scream?
太意外了 我喜欢
That was a great scream. I love it.
天啊! 我简直不敢相信它竟然还合身
Oh, my God! I can't believe it still fits.
- 我知道  - 看看我
- I know.  - Look at me.
顺便提一句 你腿比我的好看
You have better legs than I do, by the way.
我整个身材就像个青蛙一样
I have a body like a frog.
- 没有啊  - 不 我有
- No, you don't.  - Yes, I do.
什么意思?
What does that mean?
就四肢很长 肚子很大
Just a big belly and long arms and long legs.
就像...
Just like...
哦 米歇尔·沃勒
Oh, Michelle Waller.
都有两个孩子了 又怀了
Pregnant again, baby number three.
- 第三个孩子了?  - 嗯
- Baby number three?  - Yeah.
- 卧槽 我都不知道她结婚了  - 呵呵
- Shit, I didn't even know she was married.  - Yeah.
这还是老爸过世后我们第一次来这片墓地
We haven't done the cemetery walk since Dad died.
我知道
I know.
天 你小心脚下
Oh, my God, watch your step.
老天 这儿几乎没怎么变
God, it has not changed a bit.
我在这儿拥有了人生第一个葡萄酒冷酒器
I had my first wine cooler here.
- 跟谁?  - 詹妮·科普兰
- With who?  - Jenny Copeland.
- 那可以理解  - 嗯
- That makes sense.  - Yeah.
哦 哇哦!
Oh, wow!
老爸生前最喜欢万圣节了
Dad loved Halloween.
谁不是呢?
Who can blame him?
够了
Scram.
出去
Get out of here.
怎么 你聋了?
What, are you deaf?
我才没聋 这可是万圣节 白痴
I'm not deaf. It's Halloween, assholes.
蛇精病
Fucking people.
天啊!
Oh, my God!
等等 他们分给我们的那个...
Wait, what was the name of the...
那个青少年精神病学家叫啥来着?
adolescent psychiatrist that they assigned us?
- 她叫啥?  - 额 叫...
- What was her name?  - Oh, shit.
- 是叫玛丽?  - 应该是玛米·莫蒂默
- Mary?  - Mamie Mortimer.
- 玛米·莫蒂默  - 玛米·莫蒂默和她那些狗屁日记
- Mamie Mortimer.  - Mamie Mortimer and her fucking journals.
又肥又大的毛衣
Giant sweaters.
毛衣怎么了?
What was with those sweaters?
超级大! 她又不胖
Huge! She's not a big woman.
对于玛米·莫蒂默 每一天都是圣诞节
Every day was Christmas for Mamie Mortimer.
老天! "你们有没有把那写进日记里?"
Oh, my God! "Did you write that in your journal?"
"没有什么是记日记解决不了的"
"There's nothing that can't be solved by journaling."
"啊你们父亲去世了? 写在日记里"
"Oh, your dad died? Put it in a journal."
- "你忘了 是不是?"  - "我老爸过世了 我觉得好多了"
- "You forgot about it, didn't you?"  - "My dad died, I feel better."
不过 她的工作也不容易
She had a tough gig, though.
我的意思是 我们不是什么好孩子
I mean, we were not good kids.
我是说 如果是你 你要怎么面对两个父亲已经不在了的孩子...
I mean, what do you do to two kids whose dad...
- 你让他们写日记  - 是 我是说 我们当时才十四岁
- You make them keep a journal.  - Yeah, I mean, we were 14.
神啊 我们都是忘恩负义的混蛋 是吧?
God, we were ungrateful bastards, though. Right?
黑你自己就够了
Speak for yourself.
我可是天使 我不知道你在说什么
I was an angel. I don't know what you're talking about.
玛姬
Maggie.
- "玛姬"  - 玛姬
- "Maggie."  - Maggie.
让我... 等下 让我看看
Let me... Oh, wait. Let me see it.
什么?
What?
我想看看你的
I want to see it.
哦 那是什么 换了个地方?
Oh, what is that, a new place?
不 还是老地方啊
No, it's always been here.
哦 在这儿 跳着欢快的舞呢
Oh, there she is, dancing away.
当然
Of course she is.
你以为我把它洗掉了?
Did you think I got rid of it?
我不知道 你是只狡猾的鸟 小喜鹊
I don't know. You're a tricky bird, Magpie.
我们怎么做到十年互不往来的?
How'd we go 10 years without talking?
现在谈这个未免太煞风景
Oh, it's probably not worth talking about now.
也对
Probably not.
让我把帽子摘下来
Let me take my hat off.
- 来吧  - 温柔点
- Come on.  - Be polite.
小喜鹊
Magpie.
噢 穿礼服在小便池撒尿也没我想的那么难
Oh, peeing in a dress at a urinal is actually not that hard.
我得走了
I'm gonna go.
不想再跳一曲?
Do you want another round?
我得走了
I'm gonna go.
嘿 嘿
Hey, hey.
等等 玛姬
Wait up, Maggie.
嘿 到底怎么啦?
Hey, what's going on?
凯文·克兰西?
Kevin Clancy?
凯文·克兰西六年前就搬到迈阿密了
Kevin Clancy moved to Miami six years ago.
他这周末就在城里
He was in town for the weekend.
什么? 这到底是怎么一回事?
What? What is this?
我看见你电话了
I saw your cell phone.
你有一个未接来电 里奇·莱维特打的
You have a missed call from Rich Levitt.
你和他上床了?
Are you sleeping with him?
玛姬 我们有时可能有所隐瞒 但那都是可以解释的
Some of us have our secrets and some of us have our reasons, Maggie.
哇哦
Wow.
所以 怎么着 你还对那个有恋童癖的人情有独钟?
So, what, you're still attracted to child molesters?
是吗?
Is that it?
他不是恋童癖
He's not a child molester.
你那个时候十五岁 他又是你的英语老师
You were 15 and he was your English teacher.
你没看到他是怎么对我的
You didn't see the way he treated me.
- 他想上你  - 你有什么资格来批评我?
- He wanted to fuck you.  - Who are you to judge, okay?
你五年级开始就有男朋友了 对吧?
You've had boyfriends since you were in the fifth grade, okay?
我那个时候十五岁了 还从来没被别人亲过
I was 15. I had never been kissed before.
- 他是我老师又怎样?  - 又怎样?
- So what if he was my teacher?  - So what?
他让我感觉很好! 他让我喜欢自己!
He made me feel good! He made me feel good about myself!
我不想听你说他让你感觉怎么样 你知道吗?
I don't want to hear how he made you feel. You know what?
你想和里奇·莱维特交往 那你去吧 我不拦你
You wanna go hang out with Rich Levitt, go ahead. I am not gonna stop you.
但我知道 当这一切都结束了 再回头看 你会发现我是正确的
But when all that shit went down, I know, looking back, I was right.
我不能再为此感到内疚了
And I can't feel guilty about it anymore.
事情还有可能会更糟
And it could've been a lot worse.
他差点就进监狱了啊 麦洛
He could've gone to fucking jail, Milo.
你知道吗?
Do you realize that?
我们私下处理这件事是他的幸运
He is lucky that we dealt with this quietly.
我知道你怪罪我 我也知道
And I know you blame me, and I know you think
你觉得我毁了你和他之间的这段热烈的感情
I ruined this blossoming relationship between you and him.
我知道你觉得我毁了他的生活 你的生活
I know you think I ruined his life, that I ruined your life,
但我只是做了我该做的事
but I did what I had to do.
听着 这和你无关
Look, it had nothing to do with you.
这都是瞎扯淡
That is bullshit.
你是我的弟弟
You're my brother.
我们应该互相支持对方
And we're supposed to be there for each other.
如果你到现在还不明白这一点
And if you don't get that by now, then,
那我想我还是再等十年再来和你说话吧
I don't know, I guess I'll talk to you in another 10 years.
- 玛姬 等等  - 这糟透了
- Maggie, wait.  - This sucks.
我今晚和你在一起真的很开心
I was having such a good night with you.
星期天 星期一 星期二...
Sunday, Monday, Tuesday...
星期天 星期一...
Sunday, Monday...
我靠
Oh, shit.
- 早上好  - 早上好
- Morning, chief.  - Morning.
看样子你的姐姐倒下了
Well, looks like your sis is down for the count.
我觉得她大概是食物中毒了
I think she's got, like, food poisoning or something.
是啊 或者是别的事
Right, or something.
我们应该来一个"兄弟日"
Maybe we should have a dude's day.
- 什么?  - 你懂的 "兄弟日"
- A what?  - You know, dude's day.
我感觉你口中的兄弟日
I think your version of dude's day
和我心中的兄弟日完全是两个概念
and my version of dude's day are totally different.
我靠
Oh, shit.
我靠!
Oh, shit!
加油啊 兄弟 你差点就成功了
Come on, man. You almost had it that time.
兰斯 这护具卡到我的蛋蛋了
Lance, this harness has my balls in my fucking throat.
我能下来了吗?
Can I please come down?
要的就是这体验 小兄弟
It's all part of the experience, buddy boy.
这东西唯一的好处就是可以看到这里那么多的美男
The only good thing about this experience is that every guy in here's gorgeous.
是啊 这里很棒
Yeah, it's great here, man.
你身边有一大群的肌肉男 太美了
You're surrounded by a bunch of hunks. It's beautiful.
加油啊 你得化疼痛为力量
Come on, you gotta use the pain. Get inspired by it.
你是谁啊? 难道你是攀岩界的法西斯?
What are you, some sort of, like, climbing Nazi?
我相信你 仅此而已
I just believe in you, that's all.
我看到你在公园里的样子了
Come on, I saw you out there working at the park.
你能做到的 兄弟 我相信你
You got it in you, dude. I believe in you.
- 加油  - 你真是一坨屎啊 兰斯
- Come on.  - You're such a piece of shit, Lance.
好啊 太棒了
Yeah, awesome. Awesome.
就这样 继续保持 兄弟
Just keep doing it just like that, man.
就是要这样嘛! 兄弟 你太棒了!
That's what I'm talking about! Boo-ya, dude!
- 敬"兄弟日" - 敬"兄弟日"
- To dude's day.  - To dude's day.
我得说 你刚刚就和我中学里的体育老师一样
I gotta tell you, you were channeling my middle school P.E. teacher out there.
你喜欢吗?
Yeah, you were into it, huh?
是啊 这很... 你很能激励人
Yeah, it was very... You're very motivating.
谢谢
Thank you.
你会成为一个好爸爸的 挺好的
You're gonna be a good dad someday. That was good.
谢谢你 兄弟
Thanks, man.
挺有趣的 我的朋友们
It's funny, 'cause all my buddies,
他们都被当爸爸这事把屎都吓出来了
they're scared shitless about the whole fatherhood thing,
我知道我已经准备好了
and, yeah, I just know that I'm ready for it.
所以这一切关于怀孕的事才那么让人泄气 你懂吗?
That's why the whole pregnancy thing has been frustrating, you know?
我只是想知道我的努力没有白费 你懂吗?
Just wanna make sure I'm not firing blanks, you know?
是啊
Right.
我猜是我想太多了吧
Guess I'm just a little paranoid.
你注意到她最近表现有点奇怪吗?
Have you noticed her acting a little strange at all lately?
我是说...
Like, I mean...
我也不知道怎么说
I don't know what I mean.
我知道 是的
I know what you mean, yeah.
我感觉她能在夏威夷怀孕 我有这种预感
It'll all happen in Hawaii. That's how I feel.
信风吹过棕榈树之间
Just in between the trade winds and the palm trees
那里的人 也有一种异域风情
and the people and, you know, exotic spices.
是啊
Yeah.
也许我们可以在吊床里面做
Maybe we'll do it in a hammock.
夏威夷绝对是造人的好地方
Hawaii's definitely baby-making country.
玛姬有时候有很多秘密
You know, Maggie can be very secretive.
比如 当我们还是小孩子的时候
Like, when we were kids and stuff,
她会在屋子的不同地方藏香烟和别的东西
she would hide cigarettes and things like that around the house.
都是一些你想不到的地方
You know, places you wouldn't think to look.
也许她在吃一些药物 对这事有点影响
Maybe there's some medication or something that's affecting things.
这只是一个想法
Just a thought.
我觉得这种事玛姬不会瞒着我的
Yeah, I don't think Maggie'd hide something like that from me.
- 我肯定你是对的  - 是啊
- I'm sure you're right.  - Yeah.
嘿 小姐 需要帮忙吗?
Hey, miss, do you need help with anything?
嗯 其实 我... 我只是...
Yeah, you know what? I'm... I just...
我的那个来得有点迟了
I'm a little late.
但不是迟到了很久 只是有一点
But not seriously late, just a little.
但我... 其实 我不需要用这个
But I'm... You know what? I don't need this.
我没事 谢谢
I'm fine, thanks.
谢谢你把那个放回去 谢谢
Thank you for putting that back. Thanks.
我还要买点什么?
What else did I need?
吐得到处都是
puked all over the field.
你是玛姬·迪恩?
Maggie Dean?
我是卡莉·范德·霍夫啊
It's Carlie Van der Hoff.
还记得加菲尔德高中吗?
Garfield High?
- 记得 你好  - 天啊 你最近过得好吗?
- Yeah, hi.  - Yeah, my God! How are you?
- 我没事  - 哦 他是卡伦
- I'm fine.  - Oh, this is Cullen.
- 卡伦 打个招呼  - 嗨
- Say hi, Cullen.  - Hi.
他是我最大的孩子
He's the oldest of my rug rats.
看看你
Yeah, but look at you.
你是来看家人的吗?
Are you visiting family?
不 我就住这里
No, no, I live here.
- 真的?  - 是啊
- Really?  - Yeah.
真奇怪 我们从来没碰见过呢
That's so weird that we've never run into each other.
- 是啊  - 我在学校雇员工会里
- Yeah.  - I'm at the school employees credit union.
- 妈妈  - 卡伦 嘘
- Mom.  - Cullen, hush.
如果你无聊的话 去车里等着
If you're bored, go wait in the car.
- 哦 我要打算走了  - 去吧
- Oh, I'm gonna be leaving.  - Beat it.
- 去你的!  - 嘿 你小心点!
- Kiss my ass!  - Hey, you watch it, mister!
回敬你!
Back at ya!
真是个小杂种
What a little shit.
你相信吗? 现在的小孩都是这样 太不听话了
Can you believe kids today? The attitudes.
- 你有孩子吗?  - 没有
- Do you have kids?  - No.
那你很幸运 因为他们都是调皮蛋
Well, you're lucky because they are little shits.
你最近怎么样了? 还有麦洛呢?
So, how are you? How's Milo?
都跟我说说
Tell me everything.
我挺好的
I'm all right.
- 你结婚了?  - 是的
- You got married?  - I did.
当然了 你总是有很多男朋友
Of course, you always had so many boyfriends.
哦 天啊
Oh, boy.
你没事吧?
Are you okay?
卡莉 你能不能... 能不能等一下?
Carlie, can you... Can you give me one second?
- 可以  - 我马上回来
- Yeah.  - Be right back.
谢谢 谢谢 哦 谢...
Thank you, thank you. Oh, thank...
我们之间结束了
It's over.
别 这次是真的
No, for real.
嗨
Hi.
亲爱的 怎么了?
Honey, what's going on here?
那些都是以前的了
Those are old.
好吧 处方单上说这些是上个月的 所以...
Okay, well, the prescription says that they're from last month, so...
亲爱的 对不起 我...
Honey, I'm sorry that...
听着...
Listen...
如果你现在还不想要孩子
If you don't want to have kids right now,
我们可以谈一下这个问题 好吗?
we can talk about that, okay?
你不需要对我撒谎
You don't need to lie to me.
亲爱的 你现在让我有点慌了
Sweetie, you're freaking me out right now.
我是个烂人 兰斯
I'm a sick person, Lance.
什么意思?
What do you mean?
自从我们结婚我就一直有外遇
I've been with other men since we've been married.
有过三个
Three.
三个男人
Three other men.
我不爱他们 我知道那不重要
I wasn't in love with any of them. I know that doesn't matter.
对不起
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
兰斯?
Lance?
他很困惑 我很同情他
Look, he was confused. I felt terrible for him.
- 嘿!  - 你没有权利干涉我的生活!
- Hey!  - You had no right!
事情总是要败露的
Things were gonna crash down eventually.
不 你只是想报复我
No, you were just trying to get back at me.
- 我想帮你  - 你毁了我的婚姻
- I was trying to help you.  - You just ruined my marriage.
- 什么婚姻?  - 混蛋
- What marriage?  - Fuck you.
听着 你很痛苦
Look, you're miserable,
如果你不敢做出什么改变 我来帮你
and if you're too chicken shit to do anything about it, then I will.
哦 所以说 你知道怎么样对我好?
Oh, so, you know what's best for me?
是的 你是我姐姐 我们应该互相帮助才对
Yes, you're my sister. We're supposed to help each other out.
- 这是你自己说的  - 这不一样!
- You said that.  - This is different!
- 怎么不一样?  - 我们都是成年人了 这是我的婚姻
- How?  - We are adults. This is my marriage.
如果你觉得那还是像样的婚姻的话 那你他妈的就是疯了
If you think that's a marriage, then you're fucking nuts, okay?
- 对不起 继续享受你的婚姻吧  - 好啊 走啊 你走吧
- I'm sorry. Enjoy your marital bliss.  - Okay, yeah, go. Leave anyway.
这根本行不通
This is not working out.
你知道什么事情很悲伤吗? 我们是好队友
You know what the sad thing is? Is that we're a good team.
是啊 要不是你的生活那么一团糟 有你在身边也很不错的
Oh, yeah, and you'd be a real hoot to have around if you weren't such a fuckup.
我们的生活都是一团糟 不是吗?
We're both fuckups, okay?
我不想再装作你还是我们两个中没问题的那个
And I'm tired of you acting like you're the healthy one
而我是那个需要帮助的人
and I'm your special needs kid.
这还有什么关系 麦洛?
What does it even matter anymore, Milo?
你复仇成功了 你成功了
You got your revenge. You got it.
我只是想坦诚一点
I was trying to lay it out on the table.
我只是这么想的
That's what I was trying to do.
- 你想要坦诚相待?  - 是的!
- You wanna lay it out on the table?  - Yes!
好啊 那来吧
Okay, then, go for it.
- 你情绪不稳定  - 你是个傻瓜
- You're emotionally unstable.  - You're a prick.
你需要看心理医生
You need professional help.
这句话还是从一个刚刚想自杀的人口里说出来的
And this coming from a guy who just tried to kill himself.
也许我遇到问题就去找个人操吧
Maybe I should try fucking all my problems away.
也许下次你得切深一点
Well, maybe next time you should cut deeper.
哦不 不要啊 不要啊
Oh, no. No, no, no, no, no, no.
卧槽
Shit.
我靠
Fuck.
别死啊 卧槽
Come on. Fuck.
活过来 快活过来
Come on, come on, come on.
对了 就这样
There we go. There we go.
对了 对了 给你
Yeah, yeah, yeah. There you go.
活过来!
Come on!
嘿 我知道我不该过来
Hey, I know I'm not supposed to come over here or anything,
但我想和你谈谈 这是你欠我的
but I want to talk to you, and I think you owe me that.
你欠我的 我就是这么想的
You owe me. That's what I think.
听着 我肯定你的姐姐不是有意那样说的
Listen, I'm sure your sister didn't mean what she said.
你怎么做到的?
So, how do you make this work?
你怎么搞定你女朋友 你儿子和我的?
Like, how do you juggle a girlfriend and a son with guys like me?
有很多像你一样的人
Well, there aren't a lot of guys like you.
谢谢 老师
Thanks, Teach.
不... 我是说 这不是很常见
No, not... I mean, it's not a pattern.
你是同性恋吗?
Are you gay?
我可以和梅琳达过日子 我也想这么做
I can make it work with Melinda, and I really want to.
那祝你好运
Well, good luck with that.
别... 你能不能... 你他妈的在干什么啊?
Don't... Can you... What are you fucking doing, man?
我不是为了这个过来的
That's not why I came over here.
- 麦洛...  - 我是谁啊? 禁果?
- Milo...  - What am I, some sort of forbidden fruit?
- 不是  - 或者说...
- No.  - Or, like, some sort of...
我对你来说是个充气娃娃? 你到底把我当什么?
What am I, like, a blow-up doll? What am I to you?
我对你很不好 我知道 但...
I treated you terribly. I know that. But...
这不是因为我不在乎或者...
It's not because I don't care or because...
或者我不尊重你...
I don't respect you...
或者我不爱你
or because I don't love you.
只是因为我是个胆小鬼 仅此而已
It's because I'm a big pussy. That's it.
我是个可悲的胆小鬼
I'm just a huge, pathetic pussy.
我永远不能像你一样
I could never be you.
如果你想的话 你可以睡沙发上
You can crash on the couch, if you want.
你读过我的剧本吗?
Did you, by chance, read my script?
读过
Yeah.
怎么样?
And?
很棒
It's great.
我会把它拿给我的经纪人的
I'll definitely give it to my agent.
再说一遍 528号公交从奈亚克出发前往港务局公交车站
Once again, this is the 528 leaving Nyack for Port Authority Bus Terminal.
如果能收回我说过的话 我做什么都愿意
I would do anything to take back what I said.
不管结果怎样 我想说对不起
For what it's worth, I'm sorry.
我爱你
I love you.
我搞砸了
I screwed it up.
我总是这样
I do that a lot, I guess.
这差不多是我的爱好了
It's kind of my thing.
但是我懂了
But I get it.
爸爸他...
Dad just...
看到了一条出路
saw a way out.
我猜你也看到了吧
I guess you did, too.
我不再害怕了
I'm not scared anymore.
我终于懂了
I finally get it.
再会
See you later.
呼吸 呼吸 呼吸 你没事的
Breathe, breathe, breathe. You're okay.
你没事吧?
Are you okay?
你没事
You're okay.
好了 说句话 随便说一句
All right, say something. Just say something.
- 我没事  - 你没事
- I'm okay.  - You're okay.
你没事 天啊 你没事
You're okay, Jesus. You're okay.
呼吸 你没事的
Breathe, you're okay.
你在这里
You're here.
我在这里
I'm here.
你在这里
You're here.
-=圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hdscg.com/=-
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: 影子
翻译: BOBO金鱼 爱喝牛奶
翻译: lubi 轩一一 黄字君
校对: 浅陷夜蓝
支持我们，欢迎购买VIP移除所有广告，具体：www.OpenSubtitles.org